Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Minions.
Minions have been on this planet
far longer than we have.
They go by many names.
Dave, Carl, Paul, Mike.
Oh, that one is Norbert.
He's an idiot.
They're all different,
but they all share the same goal.
To serve the most despicable
master they could find.
Boss!
Making their master happy was
the tribe's very reason for existence.
But that's not to say
that they didn't have other passions.
Huh?
Finding a boss was easy.
But keeping a boss,
therein lies the rub.
Nope,
it wasn't easy for these guys.
But they never gave up.
With the emergence
of the Stone Age
came the rise
of a new species.
Man was very different
from the dinosaur.
He was shorter, hairier,
and way, way smarter.
The Minions took
an instant liking to man,
and helped him
the best they could.
Oh, no, no.
Eh?
Poor man.
So trusting, so fragile.
So, so delicious!
Their quest for a boss
put the Minions front and center
for some of civilization's
most historic moments.
Anubis!
Ancient Egypt
held great promise.
Okay! Pancake!
But it didn't last long.
Hmm. Oh!
Ow!
The Dark Ages were
actually fun times.
Their new master
had a tendency
to party all night
and sleep all day.
Ooh!
Oh.
But eventually,
the party was over.
They bounced from
one evil boss to another,
but they never seemed
to find their perfect fit.
One particular employer
took their failure very, very badly.
Huh?
The Minions had no other
choice but to keep moving.
Oh.
And then,
when all hope seemed lost,
they found sanctuary.
The Minions were safe!
Years passed as the
Minions forged their own civilization.
They truly made
a life for themselves.
But something just wasn't right.
They felt empty inside.
Without a master,
they had no purpose.
They became aimless
and depressed.
If this continued any longer,
the Minions would perish.
But all was not lost
for one Minion had a plan.
His name was Kevin.
He was excited to share
his idea with the tribe.
He'd been preparing
for days, weeks, months.
But now he was ready.
Buddies!
Kevin would leave the cave...
...go back
to the outside world,
and he would not return
until he had found his tribe
the biggest,
baddest villain to serve.
But he needed help.
Me!
Bob was eager to go,
But Kevin felt he was
just not strong enough
for the dangerous journey ahead.
Uh, no.
Luckily, someone stepped up.
Stuart!
Huh? Me, me?
Oh! Thank you.
Truth be told,
Stuart had no idea what he was chosen for...
...but was thrilled
it made people cheer for him.
Thank you.
Me!
Eh, okay.
Eventually,
Bob's energy and enthusiasm,
but mostly lack of other volunteers,
changed Kevin's mind.
The tribe said their farewells.
Kevin had given them something
they hadn't had in a very long time.
Hope.
Bob!
Hey, Tony!
Tom...
Chris...
Hey, Bob.
Oh.
Bye-bye.
Kevin felt pride.
He was going to be
the one to save his tribe.
Stuart felt hungry mostly.
He was going to be the one
to eat this banana.
And Bob...
Bob was frightened
of the journey ahead.
Ah. Okay.
Okay. Okay.
And they were off.
Off to find their new boss!
Huh? Kevin!
Huh?
Huh? Banana!
Uh, Stuart?
Banana. Banana!
Ugh! Ugh! Stuart!
Stopa!
Uh, Bob! Stopa!
Huh? Oh!
Bob!
Huh?
Uh, no, no.
No, no. No, no, no.
Profiterole.
No, no, no!
Stuart...
Ah!
Oh, look at that one!
Whoa!
Peace!
Make love, not war!
Peace and love!
Boo-ya!
Boo-ya! Boo-ya!
Hey, hey, hey, oh.
Kashmiri?
Boo-ya!
Boo-ya! Boo-ya!
Oh.
Banana!
- Hey! Hey, taxi!
- Hey! Hey!
Oh.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Banana! Hey, hey!
Stuart! Hey, oh!
Kevin!
Bob!
Oh. Bello!
Huh? Oh.
Ah! Bob!
Huh? Whoa!
Women's bell bottoms
and tie-dye shirts marked down.
Check out our wide selection
of go-go boots and miniskirts.
Bob!
Okay.
Huh?
Bob!
The store is now closing.
Hey, what are you doing?
Bob!
Give me that!
Kevin!
Oh. Oh.
Ah.
Huh?
Oh.
Oh. Hey!
...buddies.
No? Oh.
Bob! Bob!
Oh.
Tim.
Oh!
Me Tim!
Mmm, thank you! Hmm?
...Stuart?
Uh, nah.
Okay, okay.
Oh. "Dating game."
Okay.
And welcome back
to The Dating Game!
Well, Jennifer...
...have you decided
which of these three gentlemen
you'll go on a date with?
Is it Bob?
Yeah! Go, Bob!
Kevin?
Kevin!
Or will it be Stuart?
Oh. Yo, Stuart!
Gosh! This is so hard!
They all sounded so cute.
Um, I think I'm gonna go with...
Stuart.
VNC!
You're watching
the top-secret Villain Network Channel.
If you tell anyone,
we'll find you.
Huh!
Sponsored by Villain-Con,
for 89 years straight,
the biggest
gathering of criminals anywhere!
Big boss.
Attend guest lectures
from esteemed villains,
make contacts in
the underworld community,
and for
the first time anywhere,
Scarlet Overkill!
Evil.
So evil.
Criminal genius!
Hey, a girl's gotta
make a living!
- Move aside, men!
- Make way.
- There's a new bad man in town...
- Excuse me.
...and that man is a woman!
Crime isn't pretty!
It's red hot!
Get to Villain-Con
this weekend.
Only at 545 Orange Grove Avenue
in Orlando, Florida.
So much fun, it's a crime.
Oh! Villain-Con, Orlando.
Whoo-hoo!
Bello! Uh, Orlando?
Ugh.
Hey, uh... Orlando?
Oh, hello.
Orlando?
Uh-huh. Ah, okay.
Thank you, baby!
Bye-bye!
Ah.
Orlando!
Hey, Stuart...
Oh, yeah! Far out!
Love is the way, brother!
Ah!
Eh, no, no, no, no, no, Kevin.
Hmm.
Hey! Stopa! Stopa! Stopa!
Stopa! Ugh!
Stuart...
Oh...
Oh, Walter, look!
These adorable little freaks
are headed to Orlando, too!
Yeah, I see that!
Hey, Walter Junior!
What's happenin'?
Tina.
Hi!
Binky.
Mmm, mmm.
What do you say we give
these fellows a ride?
Yay! New friends!
All aboard the Nelson Express!
You, one-eye!
You're sitting next to me!
Okay.
Stuart!
Glad we came along before
some weirdos picked you up!
Who wants apple slices?
Ah, ah! Ooh, ooh!
Oh, you, too!
Growing boy-like creatures
need their strength.
Okay.
Heck, yeah!
Thanks, man!
All righty! Who needs
to stretch their legs?
Yeah!
Yes! Me, me, me!
Sweet!
You guys wait here,
we'll be right back.
Okay, Nelsons, let's do this!
Go, go, go!
Okey-dokey. On the road again.
Dad! We got company!
It's because I tripped
the alarm. I stink!
Hey, we all make mistakes, sugarplum.
You're still learning.
Huh! What?
- Your father's right, Tina.
- Reload!
He wasn't this good
at being evil overnight!
Reload!
Your time's coming.
It's jammed!
Huh?
Okay, who did that?
- Uh... Stuart!
- Huh?
That was great!
Thank you!
Say, fellas,
can we get personal
for just a second?
Why are you going to Orlando?
Come on. You can tell us.
You're going to Villain-Con, aren't you?
Villain-Con.
Wow! So many bad guys
in the car. What fun!
I knew it!
I knew you were villains!
Didn't I, honey?
What a small world!
Hope we're not in rival gangs.
Binky! Joke!
Babies, huh?
Yay.
Big boss!
When we get to Orlando,
I'm gonna get all my favorite
villains to sign my magazine!
Dumo the Sumo!
Boss!
Oh, Kevin,
you don't wanna work for him!
He ate his last henchmen!
Uh...
Frankie Fish Lips.
He lives in the ocean.
Boss?
Oh...
Can you breathe underwater?
Uh, so-so.
Oh, oh, oh!
Look at her!
Scarlet Overkill!
The coolest super-villain,
like, ever!
She started out as your average little girl,
braces, pigtails.
But by the time she was 13,
she built a criminal empire!
If I was a Minion,
that's who I'd want to work for!
Oh.
Here we are!
Beautiful Orlando!
Yeah! We're here!
Orlando!
Hey, gang, watch this!
Welcome to Billy Bob's Bait Shop.
How can I help you?
Yeah, hi.
Uh...
We're here for, uh,
so much fun, it's a crime.
Whoo-hoo!
Villain-Con!
All right!
Here we go!
Well, this is it!
I wanna tell you, and I really mean this.
I really appreciate what you did
back there with the cops.
Really!
Dad!
It's Frankie Fish Lips!
I can smell him from here!
Junior!
Get my camera!
Good luck in there, boys!
I hope you find what
you're looking for!
Bye!
Villain-Con!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Okay!
Oh!
Any evil talents?
Not bad.
What about you?
Any evil talents?
Uh...
Bello!
La, la, la!
Eh?
That's not evil or a talent.
Bello!
Ha-ha!
No?
I'm sorry! But I'm not looking
for any more servants,
for I, Professor Flux,
have invented
the world's first time machine!
Every time I visit the future,
I bring my future self back to help me.
Hello!
Oh.
Move that over there,
Professor Flux from two weeks from now.
As you can see,
I don't need any help.
Oh, way to go, guys.
We killed the original!
Please!
Eh...
Villain-Con presents our keynote speaker,
Scarlet Overkill!
The world's first
female super-villain!
Appearing right now in Hall H!
Bob! Stuart! Buddies! Hey!
Buddies!
Scarlet?
Kevin!
Are you ready...
Yeah!
...for Scarlet Overkill!
Doesn't it feel
so good to be bad?
Scarlet! Scarlet! Scarlet!
Yes!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Whoa.
Whoo-hoo!
Awesome!
Yeah!
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
Wow! Thank you!
Scarlet! Scarlet!
Thank you so much!
Okay.
Ah.
When I started out,
people said a woman
could never rob
a bank as well as a man!
Well, times change!
I love you, Scarlet!
Look at all those
faces out there!
We are all so different!
But we have one
thing in common.
We were born with flippers!
No? Just me? Okay.
We have big dreams!
And we will do anything
to make them come true!
Have any of you ever dreamt
of working for the greatest
super-villain of all time?
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
Well, what if
I were to tell you
that I am looking
for new henchmen?
Hey, boss! Boss!
I truly believe
somewhere out there
is a villain with the potential
to serve greatness!
And it could be any of you.
Whoa!
Although,
let's not kid ourselves.
Truly,
the only men for this job
are Kevin and his Minions!
- Huh? But... But...
- Ten times the evil
in half the package!
I am just in awe!
Let's hear it for Kevin.
He saved his tribe!
Kevin! Kevin! Kevin!
Kevin! Kevin! Kevin...
Hey! Kevin. Hey. Hey!
Argh!
So, how should we
do this? Hmm.
Oh.
You see this
tiny little trinket?
Well, just take it from my
hand and you've got the job.
No big deal,
it's almost too simple.
Uh...
Oh, come on!
Don't be afraid.
Just take the stone
and get that job! Come on!
Oh, okay.
...Boss!
That job is mine!
Ooh!
Now go easy on me.
Whoops!
Love the costume!
Ha!
Uh...
So cool!
Tim? Tim!
Uh...
Oh, no, Bob!
Ah! Tim! Tim!
Is no one good enough?
Bob!
I got it! I got it!
Ah!
Didn't my speech inspire anyone
to rise up and
prove themselves worthy?
All these villains and
yet I still have the bear.
Stuffed bear!
Why am I holding a bear?
Who has the ruby?
Wow! Who...
Who are you,
my knights in shining denim?
...Stuart.
...Bob.
Minions!
That was incredible!
Behold! The last
creatures you'd expect
to win the day have emerged victorious!
Everyone, meet my new henchmen.
The Minions!
Kumbaya! Kumbaya! Kumbaya!
Kumbaya!
Hey!
I know those guys!
I gave them a ride here!
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Buckle up, boys!
Next stop, England.
Oh...
Bello?
Hey, Kevin! Eh?
Boss? In England?
Nah, Boss!
Ah, uh... Bello, Kevin?
...England?
Uh-huh... Boss?
Scarlet Popapil. Ah.
- Bello? Bello!
- Bello?
Oh!
Wow!
Ah!
Here we go! There.
By the way,
I really like your bear.
Herb! My baby!
You know I am!
How'd it go?
Were you evil?
So evil!
Oh!
A little bird
dropped this off today.
It's me,
I'm the "H."
Also, there was no bird.
Also me.
Herb, seriously,
I wanna dig up that William Shakespeare
so he can see
what true writing is.
I love it!
Ah, that works out because I love...
Well, I love... too.
Ah, the love, ah!
Oh! Oh, ah.
Oh, boys,
could you come here, please?
Meet my husband, Herb.
Inventor, super genius, fox.
Herb, these are
the new recruits.
Kevin, Stuart, and that
cute little one is Bob.
Hey, Bello!
Right on!
You guys are crazy
little and way yellow,
And I dig that!
Sweet, man!
Ah, ah.
Whoa!
I know, right?
Ah!
Just a few things I
stole to help fill the void.
Whoa!
...mega ukulele!
Checkin' out my can?
We stole that
because finally someone
expressed my love of
soup in painting form.
Wow!
Ooh!
Okay, listen up!
It is time to get down to business.
Do you know who this is?
Uh...
This is Queen Elizabeth,
ruler of England.
Oh, I love England.
The music, the fashion.
I'm seriously thinking
about overthrowing it someday.
Ooh!
Anyway, this pale
drink of water oversees it all.
I'm her biggest fan,
love her work!
And I really, really,
really want her crown.
Steal me the crown
and all your dreams come true.
Respect! Power!
Banana!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Ha!
Henry!
...England. Uh...
...England...
Oh, uh...
Hmm.
Heh.
- Wow!
- Whoa.
Ooh-la-la.
No!
Oh, no.
Don't get too close, boys.
When it's completed,
it'll be my ultimate weapon.
But right now, it's leaking radiation
like you would not believe!
So, you're here for gear.
Whoa!
Bob, Robert, Bobby, my boy.
You get my far-out stretch suit.
Wow!
Kevin, Kev-bo,
Seventh Kevin,
you are the proud owner
of my lava lamp gun.
Ah?
This baby shoots actual lava!
Ooh!
Pretty cool, right?
And finally, Stu. Stu-art,
Stu-perman, Beef Stu.
I got you the coolest invention,
probably ever.
Oh.
Hypno-hat!
Uh, oh.
Uh...
You can use it to
hypnotize anyone. Anyone!
Oh, you look so great!
I feel like a proud mama
with three
dashing evil sons.
Uh, Scarlet, Scarlet...
No, no. Don't say anything.
I won't understand.
It's getting late.
You've had a big day,
you must be exhausted!
Boing, boing, boing,
boing, boing...
Wow! These cats
are pumped!
Well, maybe I'll settle them down
with a bedtime story?
Ha-ha!
How does that sound, Bob?
Bob. Bob! Bob!
Oh! Bedtime porry?
That is a groovy idea!
I'll go get some cookies and warm milk.
This is gonna be so fun!
...bedtime porry.
Oh, yes, I've got a really,
really good bedtime porry.
Once upon a time,
there were three little pigs.
One fateful day, the pigs
encountered a big, bad wolf...
...who had a wonderful
surprise for them!
The wolf offered the three
piggies and all their friends
a job working for her.
Everyone would be so happy!
All the three
little piggies had to do
was just steal one little crown
that the beautiful wolf
had wanted
ever since she was
a penniless little street cub,
unloved and abandoned.
But that crown would mean
she was a princess,
and everybody loves a princess!
So the wolf sent the piggies
to get that crown.
But the little pigs
weren't up to the challenge.
They failed their mission.
So the wolf huffed and puffed,
and she blew them off the face of the earth!
Yo, po, po!
The end.
Good luck getting
that crown tomorrow, little piggies.
I know you won't disappoint me.
Um.
Okay.
...Scarlet.
Which way is the loo, please?
Hmm.
Oh, thank you.
Ah.
Bello.
- Uh...
- ...please.
You're not allowed in without an adult.
Scram, hooligans!
Oh.
Uh, mm.
Ooh...
Oh, la...
Stuart...
How many tickets, please?
...please.
Enjoy yourself, love.
Thank you!
It was nowhere near Hyde Park!
Bob's your uncle.
Huh, hmm.
Okay.
Huh? Ah!
He-hey.
Okay.
Hey!
What are you doing here?
This is a restricted area!
Hands in the air!
No...
Stop that!
Get back.
Yay!
Ah!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Bob, Stuart...
So...
So, you came for
the Queen's crown, did you?
Well, you're gonna
have to get through me!
The Keeper of the Crown!
Ow! Hey!
You think it's
funny to mock the elderly, do you?
Uh...
I've been up here for decades,
just waiting for someone to try
and steal the Queen's treasure!
Okay.
What are you saying?
Never mind, don't care!
Oh, no!
Oh, no, you don't!
Oh, flippin' heck!
What's goin' on?
Bob...
Eh... Hmm.
Wow.
Hello!
Huh?
Stone the crows!
Stop him, lads!
Wait!
Go for the legs!
Gordon Bennett!
Kevin!
The Queen's
been kidnapped, Sarge!
Blimey!
Hyah! Hyah!
Ooh!
Ha! Boo-ya!
Huh. Hyah! Hyah!
What's going on?
Bello!
Oh, my goodness!
- Whoa!
- Ha-ha!
No!
Gentlemen do not
steal ladies' crowns!
Huh? Hmm?
Huh?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, dear!
Ah! Ahhh!
Yeah!
You scoundrel!
After them! Uh-oh.
Stop the blighter!
Go on, grab him!
Huh?
Huh? Oh.
Cor, blimey!
One of England's most famous
myths has become a reality
as a new king has been crowned.
Bob, who appears to be
a bald, jaundiced child,
has pulled the famed sword
right from its stone,
which, legend dictates,
makes him the new king.
Tiny yellow traitor!
England!
England! England!
England! England...
Ha, ha!
Bello!
Cut!
Hey, Bob.
- Hello, King Bob.
- Uh...
Welcome to Buckingham Palace.
Uh, no.
Oh, what's the matter,
Your Majesty?
Whatever's bothering you,
we can make it right.
Just name it!
Oh.
Buddies!
Buddies! Buddies!
Oh.
Uh...
King Bob!
Long live the king!
...Bob...
...King...
So...
King Bob!
Oh... Yeah!
King Bob! Wait!
- Wow!
- Whoa!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh...
Yee-haw!
King Bob!
Hyah!
Hmm? Huh! Ah!
Yes, King Bob. Oh.
King Bob?
Ah, Claire.
Mmm, Tiffany.
Rawr!
Ball!
How dare you!
Scarlet!
Don't you "Scarlet" me,
you backstabbing little traitors!
Using Herb's invention
to steal my crown?
I feel used.
Not gonna lie.
You stole my dream!
I was going to conquer England someday!
There was gonna be a coronation,
and I was going
to be made Queen.
Every moment was planned.
I'd wear a dress so sparkly,
it glowed!
And everyone who ever
doubted me would be watching,
and they would be crying!
I was going to be
the picture of elegance and class!
And you pinheads screwed it up!
No, no, no!
No, no, no, King Bob!
You cannot just abdicate the throne!
Who invited the square?
And you definitely cannot just
give the job to this woman!
There are laws!
Boss.
...Boss.
...Scarlet Popapil!
King Bob has officially changed the law,
Clearing the way
for Scarlet Overkill
to be crowned Queen of England!
She will be coronated
at London's historic Westminster Abbey.
If I wasn't so polite,
I'd say this spells certain doom for the country,
if not the world.
But I'm so very polite
that I shall keep my mouth shut.
But, seriously,
we're all in big trouble.
Scarlet! Scarlet!
I don't have time
to answer any questions.
I just want to
thank the Minions
for going above and
beyond the call of duty.
You are three tiny, golden...
...pill shaped
miracle workers,
and you have stolen
not just England but my heart.
Scarlet, over here!
Pardon me?
Eh?
Wow! So many!
Good for you!
Well, you'll all
get what you deserve.
Serve!
...serve!
Whoo-hoo!
Oh.
Go ahead, go ahead.
Uh...
I don't want you to take this
the wrong way, but I hate you.
I thought I could get over what you did,
but I feel so betrayed.
I think...
Yes, I think we're gonna have to break up.
And it's not you.
Wait, hold on.
It is you. It's 100% you!
No, no.
So get comfortable, Minions.
Get real, real comfortable.
Because this is where
you're going to spend
the rest of your
worthless little lives.
All right!
Let's do this!
Herb!
Who's this handsome "Herb" fella?
No, my name is "Blerb."
I'm a dungeon master.
Prepare for torture,
which I do!
All right, are we comfy?
Doesn't matter! This is torture!
- Huh.
- Oh.
Wow! Harder than I thought.
Next machine!
Oh, welcome to Hang Town!
Population, you!
Oh.
Whoo-hoo!
Cut it out! This is
really unprofessional!
There's no laughing
in the dungeon!
I wanna see tears and
I wanna hear screams,
or I'm gonna get... Wait!
Hey!
Ooh! I've got a groovy idea!
Ah!
Look at this!
Argh!
Hello!
Will the future king, Herb Overkill,
please come upstairs
to prepare for the coronation?
Well, I hope you learned
your lesson for today.
And by the way, it was me,
Herb, the whole time!
I don't even know
anyone named "Blerb"!
Uh, Herb...
Oh. Huh.
I am hours away from becoming
the Queen of England!
I know!
It's a gas!
I will finally get my crown.
Yeah.
It's all I've ever wanted.
I'm going to be so happy.
But let me ask you
something, Fabrice.
Does that look like this to you?
Mrs. Overkill,
the hair in that picture,
it's just two wavy lines!
Oh, so, what,
now you're an art critic?
I drew that when I was five years old!
Get out of my sight!
Bye, Fabrice!
I liked him. He was fun.
So, what do you
think of the dress?
Oh, it's so beautiful.
So fashion-forward.
So Valentino.
Gave it a sweetheart
neckline because you're my sweetheart.
The high collar
and cinched waist
reflect a simpler,
more violent time.
The material is a blend of taffeta
and high-density body armor.
Fully armed and loaded.
And that glow,
that's nuclear.
Nice. Just one more
thing to do.
Gotta look good for the public.
Ugh.
Do you mind?
My pleasure.
Little tighter, sweetie.
Come on, I can take it.
Little tighter.
Tighter!
Must have tiny waist.
Seeing stars, seeing stars!
Losing feeling in my legs. Perfect!
Tie it, tie it, tie it, tie it.
Huh?
Ah. Bob! Stuart!
Eh?
- Ooh! Bello!
- Ooh-ooh!
Ah! Oh.
Ah.
Huh!
- Eh, eh, Kevin...
- ...Scarlet.
Ah!
"Porry Scarlet."
- He, he!
- ...Boss.
Oh.
Ah, okay!
Huh?
I love you, Scarlet!
Queen wave, queen wave!
Queen waving!
I am so, so excited!
This is perfect!
Everyone looks so nice!
Oh! Oh, you are just adorable!
Oh, yes!
And that music, oh!
Who is that organist?
She is good! Right?
She looks like an Edna.
Edna, you are very good!
Who was that? Whoa!
Thanks for doing this,
padre. Big fan.
Uh-huh.
Come here,
let me squeeze you!
Oh, you are so squishy!
...Scarlet.
Go, go, Go!
Ouch! Ouch!
...sayonara!
Ciao...
Bob...
Stuart!
Aww! Oo-ooh!
Okay!
Oh! Beh...
Will you to your power
cause law and justice...
...Popapil!
Oh!
Ah...
Hmm? Ah...
Huh? Uh... Uh...
Stopa!
Bah!
In mercy...
No, no, no!
Do you, Scarlet Overkill...
Yeah!
Huh? Oh?
No!
Uh, mmm...
...Bob.
I proclaim thee,
Scarlet Overkill,
the Queen of England!
Oh! Huh?
Kevin!
Huh?
Scarlet! Scarlet, my queen?
Somebody help me!
Come on, come on!
Lift on two. One, two!
One, two!
Huh?
Scarlet! You're okay!
He tried to kill me!
Uh, no...
Villains, this is no longer a coronation!
It is an execution!
Get them!
Whoa, Nelly!
Run, fellas, run!
Come back here, you!
Ah!
Uh?
Hyah!
Aah!
You're mine!
Stuart, Bob! Uh...
Oops!
Oh!
Hey! I got one!
Tim!
Huh?
Oh? Aww! Oh!
Uh? Eh?
Tim!
Stuart! Bob!
Buddies!
Mind the gap.
Mind the gap!
Mind the gap! Mind the gap!
Mind the gap.
Mind the gap!
He won't get away!
He won't escape us!
Huh?
What about this one?
Why did the queen go to the dentist?
To get her teeth crowned.
Heh!
Tell us another one, Lizzy!
Uh, uh...
Bello!
Oh!
It's you.
Everyone, this is one
of the little fellows
who stole the monarchy from me.
And how's that
working out for you?
Uh, Scarlet...
Oh, yes, yes, I saw what
was going on on the telly.
Uh, telly?
What was meant to
be the coronation of
Scarlet Overkill has
gone terribly wrong as...
Move!
Kevin, Kevin,
I know you're out there.
You think you've gotten away?
Well, what do we have here?
Bello!
Oh, my goodness!
Bob? Stuart?
Which one shall I kill first?
Little Bob? Stuart?
Bob! Stuart!
I will do it, Kevin,
if you are not back here by dawn!
Oh, my!
No!
...buddies!
...Scarlet.
There he is!
Follow me!
Ah! Ha-haa!
Who the man, eh?
Uh... Oh!
Oh.
Harder! It's just my head.
Oh, no!
This way! Let's get him!
Go, go, go!
No!
Huh?
Oh.
Ultimate weapon initiated.
Activation in three, two, one.
Bello.
Huh?
...buddies!
This is it, boys!
Things do not
look good for you.
Oh, and I'm keeping the bear.
Tim!
You're not gonna need him
where you're going.
Heaven.
Huh? Uh... Aah!
Shoosh, shoosh,
shoosh, shoosh! Oh!
Huh? Ah!
Bye-bye. Say bye-bye,
Bob. Bye-bye!
Huh?
Oh, whoa!
Wait, what? How did he...
Hold my bear.
Huh?
Yippee! Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Kevin!
So, that's your plan?
Make yourself a bigger target?
Huh?
K-K-Kevin? Hey!
...Kevin!
Whoa!
Ow!
And so help me,
I never wanna
see another one of
your goofy, bug-eyed
faces ever again!
Scarlet! Scarlet! Scarlet!
What?
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me!
Oh no, you don't!
Whoa!
And just for the record,
my little deviled eggs,
you can thank Kevin
for what I'm about to do to you!
Ow! Ow!
Bob! Stuart!
Buddies!
Tony!
Tom!
Chris!
You the man!
Buddies! Mazel tov.
Ugh! Ew!
Ooh! Aah! Kevin! Kevin!
Enough! This ends now!
Kevin!
You imbecile!
Have fun exploding!
Baby!
What's the rush?
Got to get out of here!
Let us go!
No, no, no, no!
Kevin!
Kevin...
Huh?
Ha-ha! Whoo-hoo!
Ooh!
Stuart?
Hmm.
Bob?
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are here today to celebrate the Minions!
Huh!
The country owes you
a great debt of gratitude.
Bob, you were a wise and
noble king for all of eight hours.
So for you,
I offer this tiny crown
for your teddy bear, Tim.
Oh, very good, Bob!
Oh, spectacular!
I'm so proud of you boys!
Oh, Stuart.
For you,
I have this beautiful,
super-duper, incredible...
Ah!
...snow globe!
Eh? Poglobe?
Uh, ze...
And look, look,
hours of excitement!
Oh, uh...
Yippee.
Uh, eh, gracias.
Stuart, we're just
messing with you!
Don't be mad at me,
it was Kevin's idea.
Kevin!
We have a much
better surprise for you!
...super mega ukulele!
Uh... Wow!
...poglobe.
Thank you.
Right. Uh...
And finally, Kevin!
You are a hero of
the highest order.
For your bravery and valor,
I am knighting you.
From here on out,
you are Sir Kevin.
Well done.
What a beautiful moment!
Kumbaya!
The nation, nay,
the world was celebrating
Kevin, Stuart and Bob.
The last few thousand years were rough,
no question,
but things were
finally going their way!
Kevin had never been more proud.
But something was missing.
Yes, good show, good show!
My crown is gone! It's gone!
Blimey!
She's lost the crown!
Oh, my days!
Scarlet?
Scarlet! Hey!
...Scarlet! Hey!
They took everything from me!
My castle! My reputation!
Things look bleak,
baby, I'm not gonna lie!
But now at least
I have my crown!
Child,
give me that back.
No, I don't think so!
You have no idea who
you're messing with!
I am the greatest
super-villain of all time!
Oh!
Were you?
B... B... Buddies...
Ah!
...Boss! Ha, ha!
Get back!
Are you really going to
allow that little penguin
to make off with my crown?
Herb.
I'm done.
For me?
Bye-bye!
Big boss!
And that is how the Minions
found their new boss.
He was cunning,
he was evil, he was perfect.
He was despicable.
Huh?
Banana!
Banana! Banana! Banana!
Cheese! Cheese! Cheese!
Gru! Gru! Gru!
Gru!
Bob...
Hey! Come back here!
Freeze ray!